Tanishk Mahajan

Digital Marketing Strategist & Business Dev

linkedin.com/tanishk-mahajan | tanishkmahajan.com tanishkmahajan@gmail.com | 8238925561

BACKGROUND

Digital Marketer with Facebook Ads experience. Google Ads Certified. Background in Full Stack Web Development and DevOps in AWS. Coming from a family of English teachers it goes without saying that I have impeccable communication and people skills. Currently MAY 2019 - AUG 2019 based in Delhi

EDUCATION

Manipal University Jaipur BTech Computer Science 2020

TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML | CSS | JS | Facebook Ads | Google Ads | Google Analytics | SEO | SEM | Copywriting | Wordpress | Shopify | Mailchimp

CREATIVE SKILLS

Photoshop | Premiere Pro | After Effects | Illustrator

SOFT SKILLS

Verbal Communication & Negotiation | Leadership | Public Speaking | Confidence | Networkina

CERTIFICATIONS

Google Search Ads (ID 48445708) Google Display Ads (ID 47898138) Google Analytics (Currently working on it)

LANGUAGES

English | Hindi

AWARDS AND RECOGNITION

- 1. Won 1st position as Best Team overall in the Inter-Delhi Debate Competition at NCJ **Public School**
- 2. 2nd position in the Inter-Gujarat Debate Competition at DPS, West Ahmedabad
- Competitions at Mount St. Mary's School

EXPERIENCE

CDATA | DevOps Engineer

JAN 2020 - MAY 2020

Deployed drivers using Docker & K8s. Implemented SSO for provider APIs and connected it to AWS console. (Certificate)

PERSISTENT SYSTEMS | Azure Developer

Built a chatbot using Microsoft Azure and Microsoft Bot Framework and integrated it to Microsoft Teams (Certificate)

MUJ COLLEGE FESTS | Full Stack Developer

AUG 2019 - DEC 2019

Worked with a team of 7 devs to develop 2 fully responsive, cross browser compatible and dynamic websites using HTML, CSS, JS, Firebase & AWS.

Links - oneiros.mext.in | abhivarta.mext.in

PROJECTS

FACEBOOK ADS

Built an ecommerce store on Shopify and ran FB Ads on it with 350+ impressions and a reach of 180+ (Dropshipping Model)

WEBSITE DEVELOPMENT

1. Developed a social networking site for bikers using HTML, CSS, JS, NodeJS, MongoDB, Express. Sign up/Login using Google/FB. Deployed on DigitalOcean for 60 days (Free Trial)

2. Developed 2 websites for Digital Marketing companies using HTML, CSS & JS

Links - iconmedia.co.in | techlane.ml

GRAPHIC DESIGN

Check out all my work on Behance

VIDEOGRAPHY

Check out the travel <u>video</u> I made while in Ladakh

VOLUNTEERING

AIESEC, EGYPT | Global Volunteer

DEC 2018 - JAN 2019

Worked with a local business for their business development. Directly served the UN's goal #8 Decent work and Economic Growth. (Certificate 1) (Certificate 2)

AASHIANA CHILDRENS' HOME, CHANDIGARH Teacher

MAY 2018 - AUG 2018

3. 1st position at various inter-school Debate Taught English & Math to underprivileged children starting from class 8 - 10 for a total of 2 months